准备好了吗
Ready?
黑面包  桔子酱  花菜浓浆  上等的大腊肠
Rye bread, marmalade, pureed cauliflower, the good bologna
还有一丁点脚趾甲
and just a hint of toenail.
左脚大拇指上的
Left foot, big toe.
完全正确
Nailed it.
小伙子们  你们也知道我对《太空狼人》
Okay. So boys, you got me a little bit nervous
的试镜环节有一点紧张
about my "space werewolves" audition,
所以我决定通过这个来体验狼人生活
so I decided to get my wolf on with this:
艾米·“獠牙”·沃尔夫特撰写的《狼人之道》
"The Way of the Wolf" by Emmy "Fangs" Wulfert.
（艾米·沃尔夫特是本剧主演两个替身的姓名混合体）
“獠牙”是一个青少年的狼人女孩
"Fangs" is a teenage wolf girl.
当她很小的时候  她在一次露营中走散了
When she was little, she wandered off on a camping trip
之后十年就都在丛林中度过  被一群狼养大了
and spent the next 10 years of her life in the wild being raised by wolves.
我还在想玛蒂是不是就这么变成现在这样了
I wonder if that's how Maddie became Maddie.
她喜欢狼  不敢相信
She likes wolves. Big whoop.
我听说范·迪塞尔梦寐以求那个角色  甚至做手术种植了狼的獠牙
I heard diesel wants the part so bad, he had wolf fangs surgically implanted.
什么
What?
而过去整整两个月  戈斯林都在吃公路上被撞死的动物为生
And for the past two months, Gosling's been eating nothing but roadkill.
他们肯定会击败我的
They're gonna crush me.
我需要你们的帮助
Okay, I need your help.
我怎么摸透特里斯坦啊  他最喜欢什么
How do I figure out Tristan? What's his thing?
不用想就知道  当然是他的嚎叫啊
No brainer. It's his howl.
好的  我来试试
Okay, yeah. I got this.
听起来五成像狼  五成像丽芙
It's like 50% wolf, 50% Liv.
你们觉得怎么样啊
What do you guys think?
- 选迪塞尔吧  - 选戈斯林
- Diesel. - Gosling.